ewanetwork.com 2013-06-02

# Privacy Policy | EWA Network

This privacy policy applies to the relationship between EWA Network Inc. and any advertiser or publisher in the publisher or advertiser programs. By using EWA Network Inc. services, you agree to EWA Network Inc. connection, use, storage, and disclosure of information by EWA Network Inc..

By visiting this website, you agree to be bound to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, do not use any services or products offered by EWA Network Inc..

This privacy policy may change at any time and continued use of this website is considered your acceptance of the current privacy policy. If you do not agree to any changes in the privacy policy, please discontinue use of the site immediately.

**Use & Collection of Information**  
EWA Network Inc. attempts to collects information from persons (1) when they are over 18 years of age, (2) when an individual or business entity requests support or services from EWA Network Inc., (3) when an individual or business entity owns and operates websites which conduct business with EWA Network Inc.. Aside from a log of any visits to EWA Network Inc., we do not collection any personally identifiable information about visitors who don't supply personal information. 

**Publisher or Advertiser Program Applicants**  
EWA Network Inc. collects personal information from all applicants for the purposes of, including but not limited to, evaluating and verifying an applicant's information for considered acceptance to the EWA Network Inc. programs. If the applicant is accepted as a member, all personal information will be kept on file for purposes of the program. By submitting information to EWA Network Inc., you agree that we may contact you via various methods, such as phone, email, or physical mail, at our own discretion. If your application is rejected, we may retain the personal information provided at own discretion. 

**Publisher or Advertiser Program Members**  
If your application is accepted to any EWA Network Inc. program, we may use and share your personal information with third parties as outlined in this policy. Information that may be shared includes, but is not limited to, website URL, email addresses, volume of traffic and leads generated, and any other information required to ensure the quality of our programs. Personal information is retained even when a member decides to terminate their account for any reason. EWA Network Inc. cannot be held liable or responsible for any use or disclosure by any third party of any personal information that we provide to that third party. If it is believed that a member is violating any of the Terms and Conditions which were agreed to, EWA Network Inc. reserves the right to share all information pertaining to that member's account. If ordered by a court of law, EWA Network Inc. will provide any and all information requested. 

**Third Party Information**  
EWA Network Inc. may collect information from individuals when an individual provides information to a third party and EWA Network Inc. purchases this information from a third party. Information provided by the third party may include, but not limited to, individual names, email addresses, street addresses, zip codes, telephone numbers, birth dates, genders, salaries, education statuses, marital statuses, occupations, industry of occupations, and any other information provided by the Third Party. EWA Network Inc. will do it's best to seek assurance from the third party that the third party has rights to transfer the Third Party Information to EWA Network Inc. and that the third party has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Third Party's Information list. 

**Cookies, Web Beacons, and Related Technology**  
EWA Network Inc. uses cookies for various reasons in regards to traffic and members of its programs. A cookie is a small piece of textual data stored on an individual's computer which is sent from a server to an internet browser. 

Cookies are used for tracking user clicks on an ad, and subsequent successful completion and crediting of leads to the correct destination, hether that is an advertiser or publisher account at EWA Network Inc.. Cookies may also be used for statistical analysis purposes by EWA Network Inc.. If you would like to reject a cookie file, you may do so within your internet browser options.

A web beacon is generally a transparent graphic image (usually a very small pixel) that is placed on a website or in an email which is used to monitor behavior of a user visiting a website or email. When HTML code for a web beacon points to a site to retrieve the image, it can pass along information such as IP address of the computer that retrieved the image, time the page was viewed and length, the type of internet browser that retrieved the image, and any previously set cookie values in regards to the web beacon.

**Third Party Advertising**  
EWA Network Inc. will share certain information with our partners and advertisers. The information, though, will generally not be linked to any personal identifiable information. When you sign up for any third party service, information may be shared with the third party and your privacy will be in accordance with the third party privacy policy. 

Third-party advertising companies are used to provide offers and campaigns to members of any of our programs. These companies may use any information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements and/or services that may interest you.

**Minors**  
EWA Network Inc. is not interested in accepting information from individuals under the age of 18. We will never knowingly solicit nor accept personally identifiable information from users who are confirmed/known to be under the age of thirteen (13). 

**Affiliated Companies**  
EWA Network Inc. reserves the right to disclose, transfer, and/or sell individual information to business entities affiliated with EWA Network Inc. at our own discretion. 

**International Persons**  
Anyone using EWA Network Inc. and its related services outside of the United States of America acknowledges that personal information will be collected, stored, and used by EWA Network Inc. in the United States. As such, you agree to the transfer and storage of information in the United States. 

**Contact Us**  
If you have questions about this privacy policy, please email [tom@eaglewebassets.com](mailto:tom@eaglewebassets.com). 

Last updated: 2011-12-12
